davidwilkersontoday.blogspot.com 2015-04-02

# About World Challenge - World Challenge

### World Challenge, Inc. – Privacy Policy

World Challenge has enacted a privacy statement and policy to ensure the privacy of our visitors’ personal information.

We are committed to excellence in the stewardship of personal and financial identity relayed through interaction on our website, store and email for our patrons. World Challenge has not and will not rent, sell or exchange the information of patrons.

World Challenge websites utilize “cookies” which enable us to determine when a visitor returns to our pages in order to know how often people visit us, when they have returned and what site they previously came from. This helps us to understand demographic information about our visitors.

World Challenge utilizes security encryption (SSL) to further protect visitor’s purchase and donation information including name, address and credit card data. This data collection is for the specific use of the transaction the user has committed to by choosing the “Purchase” button in these site areas. These sites also use a user id and password unique for each patron, for creating secure transactions.

### Opt-Out

World Challenge maintains an “opt-out” policy for visitors who have signed up for automatic email correspondence allowing you to discontinue this service. You may contact us online using our contact form or by calling 903-963-8626 and we will remove your name and email address from our distribution list.

### Changes to this Policy

World Challenge reserves the right to modify this privacy policy without advance notice.

### Use of Links

  1. Throughout our Web pages, we provide links to other servers which may contain information of interest to our readers. We take no responsibility for, and exercise no control over, the organizations, views, or accuracy of the information contained on other servers. Creating a text link from your Web site to our site does not require permission. 

  2. ### Use of Text and Images

If you would like to publish information that you find on our Web site, please contact us via the form [here](http://www.worldchallenge.org/contact). Where text or images are posted on our site with the permission of the original copyright holder, a copyright statement appears at the bottom of the page. 

  3. ### Accessibility

This Web site is designed to be accessible to visitors with disabilities, and to comply with federal guidelines concerning accessibility. We welcome your comments. If you have suggestions on how to make the site more accessible, please contact us via the form [here](http://www.worldchallenge.org/contact).

  4. ### Reading or Downloading

We collect and store only the following information about you: the name of the domain from which you access the Internet (for example, aol.com, if you are connecting from an America Online account, or princeton.edu if you are connecting from Princeton University's domain), the date and time you access our site, and the Internet address of the Web site from which you linked to our site.

We use the information we collect to measure the number of visitors to the different sections of our site, and to help us make our site more useful to visitors.

  5. ### Online Profile Updates and Donations

If you complete the Profile update form and share your personally identifying information, this information will be used only to provide you with more targeted content. We may use your contact information to send further information about our organization or to contact you when necessary. You may always opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the "Opt Out" section below.

  6. ### Sending us an Email

You also may decide to send us personally identifying information, for example, in an electronic mail message containing a question or comment, or by filling out a Web form that provides us this information. We use personally identifying information from email primarily to respond to your requests. We may forward your email to other employees who are better able to answer you questions. We may also use your email to contact you in the future about our programs that may be of interest.

We want to be very clear: We will not obtain personally identifying information about you when you visit our site, unless you choose to provide such information to us. Providing such information is strictly voluntary. Except as might be required by law, we do not share any information we receive with any outside parties.

If you sign up for one of our email lists, we will only send you the kinds of information you have requested. We won't share your name or email address with any outside parties.

  7. ### Kids and Privacy

For children who visit our site, special rules apply. We do not request personal information about children, such as first and last name or street address and city. When kids send email to us, their online contact information (email address) is not used to re-contact them and is not maintained in retrievable form.

  8. ### Questions about our policies

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us [here](http://www.worldchallenge.org/contact).
